[
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "A shopkeeper bought a TV for ₹18,500 and sold it for ₹22,750. What is the profit?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "4250",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Evaluate: 15 × (24 − 16) + 12",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "132",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Fill the missing number: −5, −2, 1, 4, __",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "7",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "If one notebook costs ₹45, how much will 28 notebooks cost?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1260",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Solve for x: x + 27 = 85",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "58",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Which rational number is greater: −3/4 or −1/2?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "-1/2",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Complete the pattern: 1, 4, 9, 16, __",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "25",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "What is the value of (3/5) + (7/10)?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "13/10",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "The temperature is −9°C. It falls by 13°C. What is the new temperature?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "-22",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Find the square of 18.",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "324",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "I have 20 dozens of pens. How many pens do I have?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "240",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Convert 0.125 into a fraction in simplest form.",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1/8",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Which is smaller: −7/3 or −2?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "-7/3",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Solve for y: 5y = 180",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "36",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "What is one-fourth of 2/3?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1/6",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "A cyclist travels 18 km in 1 hour. How far will the cyclist travel in 7 hours?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "126",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Evaluate: (64 ÷ 8)²",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "64",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Fill the missing number: −18, −12, −6, 0, __",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "6",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "If one chair costs ₹1,350, how much will 9 chairs cost?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "12150",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Solve for x: 4x − 18 = 62",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "20",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Which rational number is smaller: −5/6 or −3/4?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "-5/6",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Complete the pattern: 2, 6, 12, 20, __",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "30",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "What is the value of (7/8) − (3/8)?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1/2",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "The temperature is 4°C. It falls by 15°C. What is the new temperature?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "-11",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Find the cube of 7.",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "343",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "I have 28 dozens of bananas. How many bananas do I have?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "336",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Convert 0.375 into a fraction in simplest form.",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "3/8",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Which is greater: −9/4 or −2?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "-2",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Solve for y: 9y = 405",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "45",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "What is one-third of 5/6?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "5/18",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "A factory produced 12,480 toys. If 3,965 toys were defective, how many good toys are there?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "8515",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Evaluate: 5 × (36 − 18) + 24 ÷ 6",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "94",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Fill the missing number: −30, −20, −10, 0, __",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "10",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "If one desk costs ₹2,750, how much will 14 desks cost?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "38500",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Solve for x: 7x + 25 = 214",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "27",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Which rational number is greater: −11/6 or −7/3?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "-11/6",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Complete the pattern: 3, 12, 27, 48, __",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "75",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "What is the value of (5/6) + (7/12)?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "17/12",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "The temperature is −14°C. It rises by 21°C. What is the new temperature?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "7",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Find the square of 23.",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "529",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "I have 32 dozens of notebooks. How many notebooks do I have?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "384",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Convert 0.6 into a fraction in simplest form.",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "3/5",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Which is smaller: −13/4 or −3?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "-13/4",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Solve for y: 12y − 36 = 180",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "18",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "What is one-fifth of 5/8?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1/8",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "A water tank holds 18,750 liters of water. If 6,485 liters are used, how much water is left?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "12265",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Evaluate: (96 ÷ 12) × (18 − 10)",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "64",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Fill the missing number: −45, −30, −15, 0, __",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "15",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "If one machine costs ₹48,750, how much will 4 machines cost?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "195000",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Solve for x: 9x − 27 = 216",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "27",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Which rational number is smaller: −9/5 or −7/4?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "-9/5",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Complete the pattern: 5, 20, 45, 80, __",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "125",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "What is the value of (9/10) − (2/5)?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1/2",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "The temperature is 6°C. It falls by 19°C. What is the new temperature?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "-13",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Find the cube of 9.",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "729",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "I have 36 dozens of apples. How many apples do I have?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "432",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Convert 0.875 into a fraction in simplest form.",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "7/8",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Which is greater: −11/3 or −4?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "-11/3",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "Solve for y: 15y + 45 = 270",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "15",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    },
    {
        "grades": [
            8
        ],
        "type": "userInput",
        "question": "What is one-half of 3/4?",
        "options": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "3/8",
        "rows": [],
        "headers": [],
        "variant": ""
    }
]